Guide to the James G. Harbord Papers 1902-1949 MS 1493
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: General correspondence
  - Subseries I.1: Correspondence A-Z
    - Correspondence "A", 1923-1924 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 1)
      Letter from Howard Angus regarding his mention of Harbord for the vice-presidency, aspirations for the presidency/Secretary of War dated August 1924, offers to buy real estate, correspondence with the War Department, copy of an Immigration Bill from 1923, correspondence regarding General Pershing. Correspondents include Henry T. Allen, Brigadier General Benjamin Alvord, General W.H. Arthur, General W.W. Atterbury.
    - Correspondence "A", 1922-1923 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 2)
      Correspondence regarding mother's death, correspondence from Henry T. Allen regarding the economic situation and unrest in Europe after the armistice, correspondence from Henry T. Allen from the Interallied Rhineland Commission (confidential, from Coblenz) on ending the American presence in Germany in 1922, draft minutes from military meetings in Europe, correspondence regarding military purchases.
    - Correspondence "BA-BE", 1941-1946 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 3)
      Correspondence mentioning the Philippines, letter regarding Harbord's support of General Petain after the war dated November 16, 1945.
    - Correspondence "BA-BE", 1941-1944 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 4)
      A pamphlet entitled "Shall the Japanese be Allowed to Dominate Hawaii?", correspondence mentioning the Philippines.
    - Correspondence "BA-BE", 1937-1940 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 5)
      Telegram regarding Mrs. Harbord's death.
    - Correspondence "BA-BE", 1934-1937 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 6)
      Frederick W. Beekman D.D.'s church sermons, correspondence regarding the Philippines.
    - Correspondence "BA-BE", 1933-1934 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 7)
      Document from the National Acceptance Corporation asking for customers to boycott Germany, correspondence with the U.S. House of Representative.
    - Correspondence "BA-BE", 1931-1933 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence "BA-BE", 1931 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence "BA-BE", 1929-1930 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence "BA-BE", 1927-1929 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence "BA-BE", 1925-1927 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 12)
      Correspondence with the Rockefeller Foundation.
    - Correspondence "BA-BE", 1924-1925 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 13)
      Correspondence with the French military, correspondence regarding the Philippines, correspondence regarding military medals and honors.
    - Correspondence "BA-BE" "Bank Deposits", 1946-1947 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence "BA-BE" "Bank Deposits", 1945 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence "BA-BE" "Bank Deposits", 1945 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence "Bank Deposits", 1946 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence "Bank Deposits", 1946 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence "Bank Deposits", 1944 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence "Bank Deposits", 1944 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence "Personal Letters Newton D. Baker", 1918-1937 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 5)
      Many references to Pershing. Confidential War Department correspondence.
    - Correspondence "Banks", 1944 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence "Banks", 1944 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence "Banks", 1936 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence "Banks", 1933-1936 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence "Banks", 1931-1932 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence "Banks", 1928-1931 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence "Banks", 1923-1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence "BI-BO", 1931-1945 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 13)
      Contains personal correspondence with and regarding the Baroness Isabelle de la Bouillerie, who sued her own family for making false charge to the German occupation and later to the French Provisional Government. She was imprisoned for a year.
    - Correspondence "BI-BO", 1931-1940 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 14)
      Correspondence regarding the death of Harbord's father and of Mrs. Harbord.
    - Correspondence "BI-BO", 1935-1937 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 15)
      Includes pamphlet, "An Intelligent and Unbiased Discussion of the Cotton Situation" produced by the Neely Bowen Company, Southern Farms and Plantations
    - Correspondence "BI-BO", 1931-1934 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence "BI-BO", 1927-1930 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence "BI-BO", 1922-1927 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence "BI-BO", 1925-1927 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence "BR-BY", 1944-1947 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence "BR-BY", 1928-1942 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence "BR-BY", 1941-1942 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence "BR-BY", 1939-1940 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 2)
      Congressional Record, Proceedings and Debates of the 76th Congress, First Session.
    - Correspondence "BR-BY", 1937-1939 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 3)
      Brigadier General Charles Burnett's Report on his inspection trip to the Philippines, pamphlet entitled "The Road to Peace-- the Short Cut and a Way Round."
    - Correspondence "BR-BY", 1936-1937 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 4)
      American Petroleum Institute pamphlet, "The Future of Free Enterprise." War Department correspondence, booklet entitled, "Generals and Lieutenant Generals in the United States Army."
    - Correspondence "BR-BY", 1935-1936 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 5)
      1936 Advertisement for helping families of veterans, "How Can We Say 'Merry Christmas' to These Little Ones?"
    - Correspondence "BR-BY", 1934-1935 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence "BR-BY", 1932-1933 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence "BR-BY", 1929-1930 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 8)
      Booklet from the U.S. Indian School, Indian Vocational School, Phoenix, Arizona, 1925: "Ten Years: 1915-1925, Selected Editorials from the Native American.
    - Correspondence "BR-BY", 1928-1929 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence "BR-BY", 1927-1931 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence "BR-BY", 1927-1928 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence "BR-BY", 1924 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 12)
      Brentano's Bookstore Advertising and Communications. Sensitive War Department Correspondence.
    - Correspondence "BR-BY", 1923-1924 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence "BR-BY", 1924-1926 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence "CA-CL", 1942-1947 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 15)
      Color copy of "Our Times, A Biblical Interpreter of the News," copies of "The Temperance Bulletin," other Christian ephemera, a copy of a talk by Winston Churchill on August 8, 1939, extract from a text of Prime Minister Churchill's report to Parliament, February 22, 1944.
    - Correspondence "CA-CL", 1941-1942 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 16)
      A Chrysler Corporation booklet entitled, "Assembly Lines of Defense," 1941.
    - Correspondence "CA-CL", 1938-1940 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 17)
      "A Prophecy on Communism," anti-Jewish statement made by "America For Americans," "Aryan Republicans" ephemera.
    - Correspondence "CA-CL", 1936-1938 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence "CA-CL", 1935-1936 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence "CA-CL", 1934-1935 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence "CA-CL", 1933-1934 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence "CA-CL", 1931-1933 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence "CA-CL", 1930-1931 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence "CA-CL", 1929 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence "CA-CL", 1927-1928 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence "CA-CL", 1925-1926 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence "CA-CL", 1923-1924 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence "CA-CL", 1923-1924 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence "CO-CZ", 1946-1947 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence "CO-CZ", 1945 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 13)
      French newspapers-- "France-Amerique du Nord", clippings from the New York Sun regarding the war (February 20, 1942), dying and illness of close friends in the military, memorandum on the European Union Question and America, by Richard Coudentiore Kalergi, President of the Pan-European Union, New York, 1945, Copy of "Declaration of European Independence," issued by the Pan-American Conference in New York on Wednesday, March 14, 1945.
    - Correspondence "CO-CZ", 1944 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 14)
      Memorandum of conversation with Mrs. Elliott Cross, August 28, 1944, on recruitment of WACS, copy of the Draft Constitution of the United States of Europe, April 1944, Advertisement "The Map of Opportunity" published by Collier's in the Interests of a Sound Postwar American Economy
    - Correspondence "CO-CZ", 1943 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 15)
      Co-ordination of European Nationalities Preliminary Draft Report of the Committee on Nationalities of the Pan-European Conference, "Peace Aims as War Weapons," by Count Richard N. Coudenhare-Katergi, President of the Pan European Union
    - Correspondence "CO-CZ", 1942 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence "CO-CZ", 1941 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 17)
      Copy of journal "Common Sense," October 1941, copy of the magazine, "The Valve World," May-June 9141
    - Correspondence "CO-CZ", 1939-1940 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence "CO-CZ", 1938 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence "CO-CZ", 1937 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence "CO-CZ", 1936 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence "CO-CZ", 1935 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 5)
      Correspondents include General Malin Craig, Army Chief of Staff 1935-1939, recalled to active duty in World War II. Colonel John Alexander Cocke, American politician and soldier who represented Tennessee's 2nd District in the U.S. House of Representatives from 1819-1827. Expresses resistance to the New Deal. Copy of the Cowles Plan, "Prosperity within Sixty Days" describing the evils of organized labor to President Roosevelt in opposition to the New Deal. Correspondence with the Honorable FB Connelly regarding the treatment of the Crow Indians in Montana.
    - Correspondence "CO-CZ", 1934 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 6)
      Letter from Honorable Frederick R. Coudert: "If the English-speaking people cannot agree among themselves, at least in time of world crisis when the fate of civilizations may hinge upon keeping the peace, everything else would appear futile." Correspondents include William Durward Connor regarding the term "liberal" and Republican politics (over the course of several letters). Anti-socialist propaganda: "Save California From the Nuts," "Wake up California! Americanism or Communism?" Invitation to view Park Avenue property, complete with advertisement booklet, Fruits of Liberalism and Socialist Pamphlet, Pamphlet: "Humanity on the March": "these older minds do not realize that Humanity is on the march; these older eyes cannot see how the forces of radio and motion pictures and press have released human minds from the corrals of orthodoxy, and started the masses into a mental trek that leads to a new world." Letterhead from Hotel St. Regis, New York.
    - Correspondence "CO-CZ", 1933 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 7)
      Correspondents include William M. Cruikshank, Captain Hamilton F. Corbett, Colonel John Cocke who wrote a book "Black Bagdad," about which Harbord writes, "when it gets talked about and as the Pacifists and the Anti-Imperialists and the W.C.T.U and all the rest of those good people begin to be aware of it and attack it, you will find that its popularity will endure." Letter in which Harbord describes his first independent command in Oklahoma in 1891: "it was only a year before this trip to Anadarko that the ghost dancing of the Northern tribes had created some uneasiness among the Indians of the territory..." And "adventurers and outlaws of the type that within the next two years were heralded over the country as "Dalton Boys." Correspondence with L. Cole, May 3, 1933, regarding Veterans' disability benefits and the use of chemical weapons by the Germans in the First World War. Pamphlet: "Can our peace machinery succeed?" Radio address of Frederic R. Coudert, February 1, 1933.
    - Correspondence "CO-CZ", 1932 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 8)
      Reviews of General Pershing's book on World War I. Correspondence with L. Cole regarding the recent Republican loss of the presidency in 1932. Letter from Major General Malin Craig, regarding the 1932 Republican National Convention and the repeal of the 18th Amendment, letter from Honorable FB Connelly regarding Republican National Convention, and regarding the death of Chief Plenty Coos who is mentioned in previous correspondence.
    - Correspondence "CO-CZ", 1931 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 9)
      Interesting period correspondence regarding a sausage, letter from General Malin Craig regarding unemployment in California and increased number of "drifters." Bulletin, "The Regular Army in Peace," address delivered before an Americanization meeting, veterans of foreign wars, in San Francisco on May 11, 1931.
    - Correspondence "CO-CZ", 1930 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 10)
      Letterhead from Chicago World's Fair, 1933, Illustrated prospectus of a book called RURAL SPORTS, 1930, a New Year's greeting print with a riding theme.
    - Correspondence "CO-CZ", 1929 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence "CO-CZ", 1929 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 11)
      Letter from a Senator Connelly telling Harbord about the death of a Native American White-Man-Who-Runs-Him, who was the last of the men who rode with Custer and his men down the Valley of the Big Horn on June 6, 1876. Newspaper clipping of FB Connelly, Harbord, and Plenty Coos when the General was made a member of the Crow tribe and was the name "War Eagle." Lots of correspondence regarding the Plenty Coos ceremony including a copy of the remarks Harbord made at the ceremony dedicating some personal land of Plenty Coos to public use. Letterhead from The Biltmore Hotel.
    - Correspondence "CO-CZ", 1928 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 12)
      Letter from L. Cole detailing the events of World War I in light of the 10th anniversary of the armistice. Correspondence regarding putting a prohibition against war in international law. Hotel advertisement for Canon Train Ranch, Wyola, Montana.
    - Correspondence "CO-CZ", 1927 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence "CO-CZ", 1926 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 14)
      Correspondence with General W.D. Connor discussing the Civil War in China, 1927-1950.
    - Correspondence "CO-CZ" (Offsite-box 6, Folder 15)
      Correspondence with General W.D. Connor regarding Harbord's role on the board to investigate the Air Services.
    - Correspondence "CO-CZ", 1924 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 1)
      Correspondence regarding Mrs. Harbord's illness from typhoid, letter to General W.D. Connor regarding the 1924 political situation in the U.S. and with Japan and China, important exchange with General William D. Connor regarding the political situation in China and the U.S., letter from President Calvin Coolidge regarding 33 individuals in violation of the Espionage Act in 1923, letter from William D. Connor, headquarters, American forces in China, on the "character" of the Chinese people.
    - Correspondence "CO-CZ", 1923 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 2)
      Letterhead of an upcoming book from what appears to be an army colleague, "My Philippine Remembrances"
    - Correspondence "Chairman of the Board RCA, Resignation and Honorary Appointment", 1947 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 3)
      War bonds stamp, interesting reminiscence on the WWI years from Mr. Lew Sweetland, also remarking on Harbord's retirement, biography as part of RCA press release announcing Harbord's retirement. Letterhead from Atlanta Biltmore hotel.
    - Correspondence "Condolence letters (Mrs. Harbord)", 1937-1938 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence "Congratulatory letters Re: Lieutenant General", 1942-1943 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 5)
      Letter detailing Japanese-American relations from Harbord's perspective, 1942 (response to General A.T. Ovenshine).
    - Correspondence "Congratulations Re: Marriage, etc.", 1938-1939 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 6)
      Harbord's thoughts on the pending war in Europe
    - Correspondence "Congratulations, Various Events- A", 1922-1931 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence "Congratulations, Various Events - B", 1922-1931 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence "Congratulations, Various Events -C", 1922-1937 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 9)
      Letters and comments on Harbord's book publication "Leaves From a War Diary," a piece written by Harbord called "Tactics" on military tactical operations, notes on Harbord's articles published in the Saturday Evening Post, taken from a diary he kept during WWI, really interesting account of the war from Fred E. Crawford at the Sun newspaper in NYC.
    - Correspondence "Congratulations, Various Events -D", 1922-1930 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence "Congratulations, Various Events- E", 1922-1929 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence "Congratulations, Various Events -F", 1922-1931 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence "Congratulations, Various Events -G", 1922-1930 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence "Congratulations, Various Events -H", 1922-1930 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence "Congratulations, Various Events -I", 1922-1931 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence "Congratulations, Various Events -J", 1922-1929 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence "Congratulations, Various Events -K", 1922-1930 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence "Congratulations, Various Events -K", 1922-1930 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence "Congratulations, Various Events -L", 1922-1930 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence "Congratulations, Various Events -M", 1922-1930 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence "Congratulations, Various Events -N", 1922-1930 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence "Congratulations, Various Events -O", 1922-1928 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence "Congratulations, Various Events -P", 1922-1931 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence "Congratulations, Various Events -Q", 1922-1930 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence "Congratulations, Various Events -R", 1922-1930 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence "Congratulations, Various Events -S", 1922-1934 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence "Congratulations, Various Events -T-U", 1922-1930 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence "Congratulations, Various Events -V", 1922-1930 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence "Congratulations, Various Events -W", 1922-1930 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence "Congratulations, Various Events -Y", 1922-1930 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence "Congratulations, Various Events -Z", 1928 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence "D", 1946-1947 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 1)
      Letter from Harbord's secretary to Madame Despecher, his previous secretary, revealing some of the respect she had for Harbord before he died. Correspondence with General Adelbert de Chambrun regarding the difficult situation in France post-war.
    - Correspondence "D", 1945 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 2)
      Letter to Colonel Fairfax Downey reminiscing about his days as a Second Lieutenant in the 5th Cavalry in the West "Indian Territory," hand-drawn postcard of the USS Cowpens "Greetings from Tokyo Bay," letter regarding the death of General Craig Malin
    - Correspondence "D", 1944 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 3)
      Comments about the "recuperative power of the French" postwar. Souvenir booklet commemorating the 100th anniversary of the Dominican Republic. Letter written in dialect about a "black boy" being shorted in pay.
    - Correspondence "D", 1943 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 4)
      Subjects include Irish-American relations, attitudes toward the Irish in 1943. Interesting account of the war in a letter to Lieutenant General Hugh A. Drum Letter showing Harbord's negative attitude toward "those women's organizations" of WW2, including WAAC, WAVE, SAP
    - Correspondence "D", 1942 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 5)
      Booklet, "Diesel, The Modern Power" published by General Motors Corporation. Letter to Ruth Davidson talking about "practice in blackouts," air raid drills in Kansas City during the war and fuel oil shortage and ration card. A denial from the Office of the General of the Armies of a request to have a letter forwarded to unoccupied France. Letter reminiscing in a very informal way about the war-- from Erle P. Dudley. Note from a tailor indicating a wartime shortage of woolens. Harbord's view on Charles Lindbergh's cross-Atlantic flight.
    - Correspondence "D", 1941 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 6)
      Telegram addressed to President Franklin D. Roosevelt pleading with him to act in the war and to leave behind the "indifference and apathy" that characterized the American position before 1938.
    - Correspondence "D", 1940 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 7)
      The Dunn Survey Forecast of the Presidential Election 1940; also Harbord's current worries about wanting to write to friends in France in 1940 but worrying that the letter could fall into German hands: "How can one write to friends in the unoccupied area under the Vichy government, and feel confident that the letter will not be censored?"
    - Correspondence "D", 1939 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 8)
      Letter from R.A. Duckworth-Ford to Honorable Henry L. Stimson urging the government to join the war effort and to stop Hitler, written shortly before news broke that Germany had invaded Holland, Belgium and Luxembourg: "Today, I believe, the United States is the custodian of the BALANCE OF WORLD POWER. If so how does the United States propose to use that power? Shall the American people, like the legendary ostrich, hide their heads in the sands of the desert, so that they may be blind to the terrors which threaten them in common with the rest of Civilized Humanity?"
    - Correspondence "D", 1938 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 9)
      Letter from Colonel R.A. Duckworth-Ford regarding the world situation and Europe, outlining reasons why Britain found itself in the losing position in 1938.
    - Correspondence "D", 1937 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 10)
      Letter regarding General Pershing; Pamphlet titled "A Nation Has a Soul as Well as a Body"- America's Flag by Miss Nadage Doree; interesting letter to Dr. Stephen Duggan, Director of the Institute of International Education, Inc. regarding the Philippines; letter mentioning Amelia Earhart.
    - Correspondence "D", 1936 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence "D", 1935 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence "D", 1934 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence "D", 1933 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 14)
      Letter from Claire Despecher regarding the situation with France between the wars.
    - Correspondence "D", 1932 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence "D", 1931 July-December (Offsite-box 9, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence "D", 1931 January-June (Offsite-box 9, Folder 2)
      Copy of an article in the Manila Daily Bulleting, "Families of Filipino Soldiers Enjoy Higher Standard of Living;" description of the Belleau Woods where Harbord fought in WWI and the need to preserve the woods with a monument.
    - Correspondence "D", 1930-1931 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence "D", 1929 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence "D", 1928 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence "D", 1936 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence "D", 1927 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 7)